[
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1108",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/defanging-an-ip-address/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P001_Defanging_an_IP_address.java",
    "name": "Defanging an IP address",
    "serialNum": 1,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-12",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2011",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/final-value-of-variable-after-performing-operations/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P002_Final_value_of_variable_after_performing_operations.java",
    "name": "Final value of variable after performing operations",
    "serialNum": 2,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-12",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Simulation", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1689",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/partitioning-into-minimum-number-of-deci-binary-numbers/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P003_Partitioning_into_minimum_number_of_deci_binary_numbers.java",
    "name": "Partitioning into minimum number of deci-binary numbers",
    "serialNum": 3,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-13",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Greedy", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-771",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/jewels-and-stones/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P004_Jewels_and_stones.java",
    "name": "Jewels and stones",
    "serialNum": 4,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-13",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Hash Table", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2942",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-words-containing-character/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P005_Find_words_containing_characters.java",
    "name": "Find words containing character",
    "serialNum": 5,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-14",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1678",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/goal-parser-interpretation/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P006_Goal_parser_interpretation.java",
    "name": "Goal parser interpretation",
    "serialNum": 6,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-14",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2114",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-number-of-words-found-in-sentences/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P007_Maximum_number_of_words_found_in_sentences.java",
    "name": "Maximum number of words found in sentences",
    "serialNum": 7,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-15",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1221",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/split-a-string-in-balanced-strings/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P008_Split_a_string_balanced_strings.java",
    "name": "Split a string in balanced strings",
    "serialNum": 8,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-15",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Counting", "Greedy", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-14",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-common-prefix/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P009_Longest_common_prefix.java",
    "name": "Longest common prefix",
    "serialNum": 9,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-16",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["String", "Trie"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-28",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-index-of-the-first-occurrence-in-a-string/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P010_Find_the_index_of_the_first_occurrence_in_a_string.java",
    "name": "Find the index of the first occurrence in a string",
    "serialNum": 10,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-16",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["String", "String Matching", "Two Pointers"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-3110",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/score-of-a-string/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P011_Score_of_a_string.java",
    "name": "Score of a string",
    "serialNum": 11,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-16",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-3146",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/permutation-difference-between-two-strings/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P012_Permutation_difference_between_two_strings.java",
    "name": "Permutation difference between two strings",
    "serialNum": 12,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-17",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Hash Table", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2000",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-prefix-of-word/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P013_Reverse_prefix_of_word.java",
    "name": "Reverse prefix of word",
    "serialNum": 13,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-18",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["String", "Two Pointers"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1662",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/check-if-two-string-arrays-are-equivalent/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P014_Check_if_two_string_arrays_are_equivalent.java",
    "name": "Check if two string arrays are equivalent",
    "serialNum": 14,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-19",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2391",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-amount-of-time-to-collect-garbage/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P015_Minimum_amount_of_time_to_collect_garbage.java",
    "name": "Minimum amount of time to collect garbage",
    "serialNum": 15,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-20",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Prefix Sum", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1816",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/truncate-sentence/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P016_Truncate_sentence.java",
    "name": "Truncate sentence",
    "serialNum": 16,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-21",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1773",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-items-matching-a-rule/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P017_Count_items_matching_a_rule.java",
    "name": "Count items matching a rule",
    "serialNum": 17,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-22",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1528",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/shuffle-string/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/string/leetcode/P018_Shuffle_string.java",
    "name": "Shuffle string",
    "serialNum": 18,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-23",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "String"]
  }
]